<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HI, I'M OLASUNKANMI DARAMOLA on Daramola-Olasunkanmi</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/</link><description>Recent content in HI, I'M OLASUNKANMI DARAMOLA on Daramola-Olasunkanmi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:15:58 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Preparation with R</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/data-cleaning-r/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2022 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/data-cleaning-r/</guid><description>Created a tool that estimates data science salaries (MAE ~ $ 11K) to help data scientists negotiate their income when they get a job. Scraped over 1000 job descriptions from glassdoor using python and selenium Engineered features from the text of each job description to quantify the value companies put on python, excel, aws, and spark. Optimized Linear, Lasso, and Random Forest Regressors using GridsearchCV to reach the best model.</description></item><item><title>Analysis of New York Police Department Civil Service Jobs Using Spark</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/spark/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2022 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/spark/</guid><description>Processed data using Map transformation and filters. Carried out aggregation using different transformation techniques and MapReduce. Exploratory Data Analysis. Utilized Data Bricks File System(DBFS) as the data storage tool. Motivation The difficulty with recruitment within the law enforcement agency in the United States has caused a significant problem that is broadly affecting the police department. The civil service is an independent body that works with the government by providing different services to the people including employment.</description></item><item><title>Machine Learning With Spark</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/machinelearning-spark/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/post/machinelearning-spark/</guid><description>Created a tool that estimates data science salaries (MAE ~ $ 11K) to help data scientists negotiate their income when they get a job. Scraped over 1000 job descriptions from glassdoor using python and selenium Engineered features from the text of each job description to quantify the value companies put on python, excel, aws, and spark. Optimized Linear, Lasso, and Random Forest Regressors using GridsearchCV to reach the best model.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/about/</guid><description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Olasunkanmi Daramola, a Data scientist currently based in the UK.
I love making sense out of data, performing data analysis and building dashboards to answer business questions.With a background in statistics, i understand how to use machine learning algorithms and statistical models to find hidden patterns in data.
I&amp;rsquo;m open to Job opportunities where i can contribute, learn and grow. I&amp;rsquo;m willing to relocate anywhere within the UK.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heskay32.github.io/myfolio/contact/</guid><description>This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree for a simple, free form service.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message</description></item></channel></rss>